[
  {
    "question": "Explain difference between static analysis and dynamic analysis.",
    "answer": "Static analysis examines code without executing it, while dynamic analysis tests the code by executing"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does the V-Model differ from the Waterfall model?",
    "answer": "adsa"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are common software project risks and mitigation strategies?",
    "answer": "adxz"
  },
  {
    "question": "Explain how software metrics are used for process improvement.",
    "answer": "eds"
  },
  {
    "question": "Explain the concept of software version control and branching strategies.",
    "answer": "ews"
  },
  {
    "question": "Explain software reliability metrics and how they are measured.",
    "answer": "xcsd"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the key differences between Agile and Waterfall methodologies?",
    "answer": "xcsdfs"
  },
  {
    "question": "Explain how CASE tools support software design and testing.",
    "answer": "dxcdsff"
  },
  {
    "question": "Explain software defect prevention strategies.",
    "answer": "kvdpjdp"
  },
  {
    "question": "Explain black-box and white-box testing techniques with examples.",
    "answer": "oojvdsovj"
  }
]